Guide to the Goddard-Riverside Community Center Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Audio-Visual Material
  - Subseries VII.3: Photographs
    - Unidentified Institution: Activities, 1940s-50s (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified Institution: Camping and Day Trips, 1940s-60s (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified Institution: Children, 1940s-60s (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified Institution: Performances, 1940s-60s (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified Institution: Staff, 1950s (Box 105, Folder 5)